displate.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Displate

Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms used in this Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms, accessible at https://displate.com/about-regulations. As used in this Policy, the terms "using" and "processing" information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

Displate processes only those data which are necessary for properly providing offered services.

The database of users is protected by law. Those personal data are specifically properly protected and secured from unauthorized access. 

Displate processes data from you during registration, this takes place exclusively within the scope of European data protection law. You may visit our website and inform yourself without having to disclose any personal information. While visiting our website, you generally remain anonymous and the connection data is provided by your internet browser each time a page is opened, e.g. the date, the duration or the name of your internet service provider will be used by us with no personal reference unless you have logged in with your username and password.

In order to provide Users with the desired services, Users provide personal information on a voluntary basis, by filling out the profile. This personal information could include:

\- First name and last name   
\- Email Address   
\- Profile Picture

The moment we use data for a purpose which requires your consent in accordance with the legal conditions, we will ask for your express consent. You can, of course, revoke this consent at any time and/or revoke the future use of your data.

## Facebook Connect

It is recommended to use Displate by logging in with your username and password but if you like you can also register with your login data from Facebook (through Facebook Connect). If you want to use this offer, please note, that with your consent the platforms and providers transfer personal and non-personal data to us. The following data are concerned:

\- general profile data from Facebook: Name, profile picture, sex, user ID   
\- birth date   
\- email address

For further details about the purpose and extent of the collection, procession and usage of the data please see the terms of use and the privacy policy of the respective platform or provider (e.g. on Facebook.com).

## Third party services

Insofar as we utilize/employ a third party service provider for this, they shall only receive the necessary data from us and are themselves obligated to protect your personal data. What is more, Displate has concluded contracts with all third party service providers and we require from them at least as strict regulations protecting your personal data as we provide by ourselves. We require your email address so that we can confirm the receipt of your registration and communicate with you (e.g. to send a registration confirmation or to deliver an ordered newsletter). 

Within the scope of the legal conditions, we can assess usage profiles using a pseudonym for the purposes of advertising, market research and to improve our services, but only insofar as you have not exercised your legal right to revoke the permission of the use of your data.

## Cookies

A portion of our services requires us to use so-called cookies. Cookies are small files which your internet browser stores on your computer. Information regarding your visit to our website can be stored in cookies. Most browsers are configured to accept cookies by default. You can, however, configure your browser so that it rejects cookies or requires confirmation from you in advance. If you reject cookies, however, it could lead to not all of our website functioning flawlessly for you.

## E-mail Communications

Displate is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission. Displate stores the basic contact data for direct marketing purposes till you lodge an objection to processing your personal data for that purpose and whether the processing took place on the basis on your consent till you withdraw that consent or till Displate will decide that data became outdated. 

In particular, Displate may send out e-mails with Displate-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions. You may also receive notification e-mails from Displate, which inform you of actions (e.g. comments, likes, follows, displays) that have been performed on the site. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please follow the instructions contained in the unwanted e-mail message. However, please note that in all cases you will continue to receive all system e-mails (e.g. those regarding forgotten user passwords) and legal notices (e.g. updates to our policies) from us.

## Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies", text files, which are stored on your computer and allow an analysis of your use of the website. The information regarding your use of this website generated by the cookie (including your IP address) is transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. In case of the activation of the IP anonymization on this website, Google will shorten your IP address within the member states of the European Union or within states that are parties to the European Economic Area (EEA) Agreement before transferring the information. The full IP address will only be transferred to a Google server in the USA on an exceptional basis, and will then be shortened in the USA. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage for the website operator. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your web browser, however, please note that if you do so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore, you can opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics by downloading and installing the Browser-Addon from the following page: [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en].

## Social sharing

Displate uses social plug-ins from Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest, including among others the Facebook "like" button, the Twitter "twitt" button and the Pinterest "Pin it" button. When these are viewed and/or clicked, a direct connection between your computer and the server of the provider of these plug-ins (e.g. Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, etc.) is created. This allows the providers to collect personal and non-personal data from you. We recommend that you inform yourself regarding the types of data covered by this as well as the purpose and scope of the data collection and further processing and use by Facebook and Twitter as well as your rights and configuration options for protecting your private sphere by reading the data protection notices at https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanatio, https://twitter.com/privacy, and https://about.pinterest.com/privacy/.

## Notifications of unlawful content

Displate may process your personal data when you report to us any potentially unlawful content on the website. This personal information could include: 

  * full name

  * e-mail address

  * address

  * phone number.

If you are a person reporting unlawful content in your own name, your personal data will be processed: 

  * for purposes necessary to comply with the legal obligations to which Displate data is subject, in particular, the examination of notifications of unlawful content, pursuant to point (c) of Article 6(1) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation), hereinafter referred to as “GDPR”;

  * in the legitimate interests of Displate, in particular, to contact you and to pursue or defend against any claims, pursuant to point (f) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR.

If you are a contact person of the person or entity reporting unlawful content, a person entitled to represent the person or entity reporting unlawful content or any other person related to the person or entity reporting unlawful content that is involved in reporting unlawful content, your personal data will be processed: 

  * for purposes necessary to comply with the legal obligations to which Displate is subject, in particular, the examination of notifications of unlawful content, pursuant to point (c) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR;

  * in the legitimate interests pursued by Displate, in particular, to ensure contact with the person or entity reporting unlawful content and to verify whether a person contacting Displate is authorized to act on behalf of the person or entity reporting unlawful content and to pursue and defend against any claims, pursuant to point (f) of Article 6(1) of the GDPR.

The provision of your personal data is voluntary, however, it is necessary for Displate to examine notifications of unlawful content. 

## Data Administration

GWD Concept Sp. z o. o. with its headquarters in (02-017) Warsaw at Aleje Jerozolimskie str. 123 a, email address: support@displate.com, phone number: 442030512777, is the controller of personal data within the meaning of the GDPR and processes personal data in order to provide services for archiving, examine notifications of unlawful content, as well as sales of products and services. GWD Concept Sp. z o. o. ensures that the rights under the above-mentioned Regulation, in particular, to obtain the information regarding the processing of personal data and to correct them, the right to bring in the cases referred to in the Regulation substantiated written request to cease processing your personal data and the right to object to the processing of data for marketing purposes.

User's personal data obtained in order to conclude a contract are stored during the contract negotiation period and until the end of the period of limitation of potential claims under the contract. The data contained in the financial settlement documentation are kept for a period of at least 5 years in accordance with the accounting legal regulations. If data processing is necessary for Displate’s legitimate interests, your data will be stored for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data is processed or until an objection to processing is filed. Your personal data obtained in order to examine the notification of unlawful content is stored for the period of limitation of claims.

In cases where it is necessary and to the extent necessary, your personal data may be transferred to entities cooperating with the controller within the scope of services provided to the controller and supporting the controller’s current business processes, in particular entities providing IT or legal services.

## Final notes

You have the right to receive information about the personal data regarding your person, to correct, supplement or delete it at any time. Please use the contact us section for this purpose.

Displate provides to their Users the realization of their rights resulting from the law about protection of personal data by:

  * The right of access to its personal data and receiving copies or replications of those personal data.

  * The right to rectification (correction) of its personal data.

  * The right to erasure of its personal data.

\- if you consider that there are no compelling legitimate grounds for Displate to process your personal data you may require the erasure of its personal data.

  * Restriction of the processing of personal.

You may require the restriction of the processing of personal data only where the processing to storage of the personal data or exercising agreed with him activities. If You consider that the data stored Displate are inaccurate or Displate is processing them groundlessly or does not want to delete them because the personal data are necessary for You for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims or for the time of lodging an objection to processing the personal data.

  * The right to object to processing the personal data.

Marketing Objection – You have the right to object to processing of personal data for direct marketing purposes. If You shall use that right the Displate shall stop processing its personal data for such purposes.

The right to object, on grounds relating to its particular situation. You have also the right to Object against processing its personal data on the basis of legitimate interest of administrator for purposes other than direct marketing, and also when the processing is for compliance with a legal obligation, for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the Displate. 

You shall indicate its particular situation which according to it justifies discontinuation of processing its personal data by Displate according to You’s objection. Displate shall stop processing your personal data for those purposes unless Displate shall provide the legitimate grounds for the processing which override your rights or shall provide that of the data subject or for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.

  * Right to data portability.

You have the right to receive the personal data concerning its which is provided on the basis of contract or agreement. Those data shall be provided to You, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format (eg. text format). You also have the right to transmit those data directly to another subject.

  * The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

If you claim that Displate is processing personal data concerning its then it may lodge a complaint with Inspector General for the Protection of Personal Data or with other proper supervisory authority.

  * The right to withdraw consent for processing its personal data.

You have the right to withdraw his or her consent at any time. The withdrawal of consent shall not affect the lawfulness of processing based on consent before its withdrawal. Prior to giving consent, the data subject shall be informed thereof.

For the execution of your rights, you may send an email to Displate at the following email: support@displate.com with your claims. You can contact the controller about any other matters regarding personal data protection at the same e-mail address.

Displate may check the identity of a person sending above-mentioned email to be sure who is having those claims. We shall answer to your claim in 30 days from receiving an email. We shall communicate with you via that email that you send to us.

Please be informed that by executing your right of erasing of its personal data you also terminate the contract for providing services electronically.
